https://www.thefutonshop.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Account
Toggle Nav
Face MasksOrganic Cotton Face MasksCopper Infused Face MasksOrganic Cotton & Silk Face MasksKids Face MasksFace Mask SetsOrganic Cotton Face MasksCopper Infused Face MasksOrganic Cotton & Silk Face MasksKids Face MasksFace Mask Sets
Face Masks
Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Kids Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Copper Infused Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Reusable Child Size Copper Infused Organic Cotton Face Mask
Copper Infused Reusable Face Mask Insert
FutonsFuton MattressesBest Selling Futon MattressesChemical Free Futon MattressesWool Futon Mattresses | Organic Cotton BeddingOrganic Futon MattressesLatex Wool Futon MattressesSpring Futon MattressesCotton Futon MattressesMemory Foam Futon MattressesGel Memory Foam Futon MattressesFoam Futon MattressesSofa Bed Replacement MattressesShiki Futons | Japanese Futon MattressesBest Selling Futon MattressesChemical Free Futon MattressesWool Futon Mattresses | Organic Cotton BeddingOrganic Futon MattressesLatex Wool Futon MattressesSpring Futon MattressesCotton Futon MattressesMemory Foam Futon MattressesGel Memory Foam Futon MattressesFoam Futon MattressesSofa Bed Replacement MattressesShiki Futons | Japanese Futon Mattresses
Tips & Secrets
Select The Right Futon Mattress
The Shikifuton Mattress
Will My Mattress Work As A Sofa Or A Bed
How To Clean Your Futon Mattress
MattressesChemical Free Bed MattressesOrganic MattressesOrganic Cotton Crib Mattresses | Natural Crib MattressesWool MattressesLatex MattressesCoconut MattressesHemp MattressesPerformance MattressesMemory Foam MattressesMattress ToppersVegan Mattresses Chemical Free Bed MattressesOrganic MattressesOrganic Cotton Crib Mattresses | Natural Crib MattressesWool MattressesLatex MattressesCoconut MattressesHemp MattressesPerformance MattressesMemory Foam MattressesMattress ToppersVegan Mattresses
Tips & Secrets
What Mattress Is Best If I Have Back Problems?
Do I Need A Box Spring?
Main Features Of Chemical Free Mattresses
What Is Coconut Coir Fiber?
Futon FramesBest Selling FramesWallhugger Futon FramesWood Futon FramesAmish Futon Frames Chemical FreeOrganic Sofas and SectionalsModern Sofa Beds & SleepersLeather Futon Sofa BedsFuton Bunk Beds and Loft BedsOutdoor Futon FramesRustic Futon FramesDaybeds and Loungers Futon FramesBest Selling FramesWallhugger Futon FramesWood Futon FramesAmish Futon Frames Chemical FreeOrganic Sofas and SectionalsModern Sofa Beds & SleepersLeather Futon Sofa BedsFuton Bunk Beds and Loft BedsOutdoor Futon FramesRustic Futon FramesDaybeds and Loungers Futon Frames
Tips & Secrets
Maximize Your Space
The Right Futon For You
Sofa Beds Vs Futon Frames
Futon CoversBest Selling CoversClearance Futon Covers FREE SHIPPINGChenille Futon CoversCotton Futon CoversLinen Futon CoversMicrofiber Solid Futon CoversOrganic Cotton Futon CoversOutdoor Futon CoversPatterned Futon CoversSolid Futon CoversTextured Futon CoversWool Futon CoversBest Selling CoversClearance Futon Covers FREE SHIPPINGChenille Futon CoversCotton Futon CoversLinen Futon CoversMicrofiber Solid Futon CoversOrganic Cotton Futon CoversOutdoor Futon CoversPatterned Futon CoversSolid Futon CoversTextured Futon CoversWool Futon Covers
Tips & Secrets
Select The Right Futon Cover
Futon Cover Fabric Options
Natural FurnitureAll Organic & Chemical Free MattressesNatural Bed FramesOrganic Pillows & BeddingOrganic Sofas and SectionalsOrganic Crib MattressesAmish Futon Frames Chemical FreeOrganic Cotton Futon CoversOrganic Cotton Dog BedsJapanese FurnitureEco Friendly Green LampsOrganic Towels & BlanketsAll Organic & Chemical Free MattressesNatural Bed FramesOrganic Pillows & BeddingOrganic Sofas and SectionalsOrganic Crib MattressesAmish Futon Frames Chemical FreeOrganic Cotton Futon CoversOrganic Cotton Dog BedsJapanese FurnitureEco Friendly Green LampsOrganic Towels & Blankets
Tips & Secrets
Organic Couches
Organic Mattresses Vs Natural Mattresses
Platform BedsBest Selling Platform BedsPlatform Bed FramesPlatform Storage BedsNatural Bed FramesBedroom FurnitureCabinet BedsBest Selling Platform BedsPlatform Bed FramesPlatform Storage BedsNatural Bed FramesBedroom FurnitureCabinet Beds
Tips & Secrets
Platform Bed Buying Guide
Platform Bed Styles
What Is A Captains Bed?
What Type Of Bed Is Good For Health?
PillowsOrganic Cotton Pillows & Natural BeddingBright Microfiber PillowsNeutral Microfiber PillowsSolid Polyester PillowsTextured Microfiber PillowsPatterned & Chenille PillowsOutdoor PillowsOrganic Cotton Pillows & Natural BeddingBright Microfiber PillowsNeutral Microfiber PillowsSolid Polyester PillowsTextured Microfiber PillowsPatterned & Chenille PillowsOutdoor Pillows
Tips & Secrets
Fabric Color Ideas For Interior Design
Bed Pillow Buying Guide
Throw Pillow Buying Guide
AccessoriesBest Selling AccessoriesCopper Infused ProductsHealth & Harmony CollectionFolding Foam BedsNatural and Chemical Free Bed PillowsShoji Screen Room DividersTables & Futon / Bed DrawersYoga Props & AccessoriesFuton Sets Free ShippingJapanese FurnitureBedding BundlesOrganic Towels & BlanketsBest Selling AccessoriesCopper Infused ProductsHealth & Harmony CollectionFolding Foam BedsNatural and Chemical Free Bed PillowsShoji Screen Room DividersTables & Futon / Bed DrawersYoga Props & AccessoriesFuton Sets Free ShippingJapanese FurnitureBedding BundlesOrganic Towels & Blankets
Face Masks
Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Kids Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Copper Infused Organic Cotton Barrier Face Mask
Reusable Child Size Copper Infused Organic Cotton Face Mask
Copper Infused Reusable Face Mask Insert
BlogCustom
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Please review the information below.
Policy - Privacy Information
TheFutonShop.com regards your online privacy as an important and serious matter. We have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to this issue. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for TheFutonShop.com.
As TheFutonShop.com continues to develop we may add new features, change the type of information we gather or the method by which it is gathered. We will adjust this privacy policy to reflect any future changes, and notify users of any personal information we are requesting. Please review this policy for changes from time to time, and contact us if you have any questions.
This privacy policy sets out how The Futon Shop uses and protects any information that you give The Futon Shop when you use this website. The Futon Shop is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Futon Shop may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@thefutonshop.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Cancel
Cancel
Continue Shopping
Add To Cart
Please wait...
Go To Checkout
